//Array of objects that holds the exam questions and correct answers data.

export const examData = [
    {question: "1. What is the capital of Argentina?",
     optionA: "1. Montevideo",
     optionB: "2. Buenos Aires",
     optionC: "3. Maracana",
     optionD: "4. Abuja",
     correctAnswer: "2. Buenos Aires"  
},
    {question: "2. The American civil war started in the year.....?",
     optionA: "1. 1776",
     optionB: "2. 1886",
     optionC: "3. 1793",
     optionD: "4. 1861",
     correctAnswer: "4. 1861"  
},
    {question: "3. A quantity in physics that needs both magnitude and direction for description is called a ________ quantity?",
     optionA: "1. Scalar",
     optionB: "2. Linear",
     optionC: "3. Vector",
     optionD: "4. Boolean",
     correctAnswer: "3. Vector"  
},
{question: "4. What was the estimated population of China as at 2020?",
     optionA: "1. 1.6 Billion",
     optionB: "2. 1.8 Million",
     optionC: "3. 1.4 Billion",
     optionD: "4. 800 Million",
     correctAnswer: "3. 1.4 Billion"  
},
    {question: "5. The largest planet in our solar system is...?",
     optionA: "1. Saturn",
     optionB: "2. Neptune",
     optionC: "3. Jupiter",
     optionD: "4. Uranus",
     correctAnswer: "3. Jupiter"  
},
    {question: "6. Who was the second governor general of Nigeria?",
     optionA: "1. Sir James Wilson Robertson",
     optionB: "2. Sir Hugh Clifford",
     optionC: "3. Lord Lugard",
     optionD: "4. Nnamdi Azikiwe",
     correctAnswer: "1. Sir James Wilson Robertson"  
},
    {question: "7. The best language for creating web pages is...?",
    optionA: "1. XHTML",
    optionB: "2. XML",
    optionC: "3. HTML",
    optionD: "4. XMTHL",
    correctAnswer: "3. HTML"  
},
    {question: "8. The driest desert in the world is?",
    optionA: "1. Atacama",
    optionB: "2. Sahara",
    optionC: "3. Kalahari",
    optionD: "4. Moldave",
    correctAnswer: "1. Atacama"  
},
    {question: "9. Which of these below is the least desired character a programmer should have?",
    optionA: "1. Willing to learn everyday",
    optionB: "2. Self encouragement",
    optionC: "3. Patience",
    optionD: "4. Coding alone without help",
    correctAnswer: "4. Coding alone without help"  
},
    {question: "10. Does a programming language called FETCH-XL exist?",
    optionA: "1. Yes",
    optionB: "2. No",
    optionC: "3. No, but they are working on it",
    optionD: "4. Yes, but not released to the public",
    correctAnswer: "2. No"  
},
];
